Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
This is Doctor Benjamin Price.
professor of ancient history.
log number four.
The fabled Necronomicon.
The Book of the Dead. is not just a myth.
The Circle of the Wise Men have found it.
And despite my warnings. they read
from the book's unholy passages.
unleashing flesh-possessing demons
so malevolent as though
the devil himself were here.
God help us.
Log number five.
We found something.
An item of great power.
Capable of sending them back to hell.
Should they return.
I have hidden it behind rune and hex.
It must remain that way...
for if unsealed. they will sense it.
They will smell its call in the earth.
Taste it on the air.
And then. they will stop at nothing...
to destroy it.
I swear to God.
he jumps out of the window.
- And he's running down the street...
- Fuck that.
- In his underwear like it's a fucking movie.
- Who the fuck just jumps out of a window?
I know. Just a stupid motherfucker.
Oh. my God. Don't tell me that's Emma. man.
- Don't answer that.
- What if it's an emergency?
Leo. it's not an emergency.
She's just freaking out
about this lake story.
Next time. please.
you leave your fucking phone in the car.
- Okay?
- Get off my dick. bro.
Come on. Let's get outta here.
You gotta be kidding me.
Come on. Don't answer the phone.
- I...
- Don't answer your fucking phone. Leo.
I swear to God. if you answer that shit.
I'm leaving.
Hold your ground. man!
Hey. hey. babe.
- You fucking...
- Baby. how's it going?
I was just about to call.
Yeah. we've just been out on the water...
Leo!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Love you too. Bye. Bye.
Jared! Let's get the fuck outta here.
Quit fucking around!
Jared!
Help!
What the... Jared!
Jared!
Jared. where are you?
Leo!
Help! Help!
Help me!
Oh. my God!
Fuck!
I got you. buddy.
I got you.
What the fuck?
♪ I bring fire when a Pop-Tart pop out ♪
♪ Born from a volcano ♪
♪ I Drain Gang like a sink drain Drano ♪
♪ Uncanny. I'm goin' hammy ♪
♪ Hit a hundred-note
streak. hit the whammy bar ♪
♪ I wrap tight like a Trojan ♪
♪ That woman is a bad omen ♪
Got a little something
for the birthday boy here.
- Wow.
- Okay.
- Gorgeous!
- Here we go.
Gone a little overboard.
- but you deserve it. huh?
- I love it.
- Happy birthday!
- Yay! Happy birthday!
- Yay!
- Happy birthday. bro.
- I'll get us some more champagne. Betsy!
- Uh...
No. Alice. Alice. Alice.
Come here.
What was that?
Are you serious with that whistle?
No. I'm just playing. okay?
But you're not listening.
This is our third bottle.
Maybe we ought to just. you know.
- slow it down a little bit.
- Yeah. it's Joseph's birthday.
We can get a little drunk.
Okay. okay.
Good vibes only. okay?
Let's. um. open presents.
Joseph.
happy birthday. bro.
This is. uh... It's from both of us.
You guys didn't need to do anything else.
Wow. Thank you. guys. This is...
Oh. it's... It's a pen.
Yeah. well. it's not just any pen.
That's a Belvoir.
These are. like. a thousand bucks.
Yeah. more. But that is not the point.
I wanted to get it so...
You know. to encourage you
to finally finish your book.
That's not very subtle. babe.
Well. to be fair.
this is the fifth book that he's started...
Actually. it's the fourth. so...
- That's the fourth?
- Yeah.
Shit. man. I'm sorry.
But if you look at Alice. with her
pictures. I mean. you know. they were fine.
Ever since I bought her that bad boy.
the difference has been incredible.
and sometimes I think
you just need a little nudge.
Yeah. Speaking of...
- And... Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
- Another one.
Okay.
- Happy birthday.
- I love the wrapping.
- No shit!
- Oh. my God.
- Yeah!
- You look so cute!
Everybody looks cute
in black and white.
You didn't tell me
you were bringing your own gift.
- It's just a small something.
- Yeah.
Nothing compared to your Belvoir.
Our Belvoir.
I just said that it was from both of us.
Thank you. both. Thank you.
No. you're so talented.
- Oh...
- Oh!
I always forget.
You Americans like to hug.
The sister-in-law side hug.
Trying to kiss my boyfriend?
What's going on?
Well. you know. we French girls
like to give hand jobs when we say hello.
Yeah. that's really classy.
Yeah. Talk about subtle. Alice.
He's just upset
because I brought my own gift.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I couldn't care less.
So why are you criticizing everything?
- I'm not criticizing. but ease up on the drinking.
- Yes. you are.
- We're celebrating. of course I'm drinking.
- I know we're celebrating.
Just fucking tone it down!
Okay.
I'm done.
- Cigarette?
- Mmm-hmm.
Promise me we'll never get married. okay?
Look. dude. she... she
didn't mean anything by it.
No. no. no. no. she...
she meant it. Yeah. yeah.
She does this to rile me up.
It's like this cigarette thing.
We're talking about having a kid
and she refuses to stop. It's ridiculous.
It's ridiculous.
Let it go. You know what he's like.
Um... Can I bum a cigarette. boss?
Mike. enough. I'm not your boss.
I just send out the checks.
You are the boss. Come on.
Aren't you freezing
to death in that T-shirt?
Nah. feels great.
It's an oven in there.
Plus. the music is way too loud.
- Yeah. I keep telling him that.
- Mmm.
Yeah? No. go on.
continue to talk shit about me to my staff.
We... We're just talking.
It's cool. Mike. I know it's not you.
Alice. would you come back in. please?
Okay. Come here.
- Don't touch me!
- Hey. hey. hey. okay.
Just relax.
Don't make me out to be someone
that I'm not. all right?
You're the one making a scene at my club.
And you make me out
to be this hysterical drunk.
Hey. I'm sorry. all right?
Now come on. let's go.
Hey. look at me.
Fuck. I just hate when you
act like a fucking child.
Don't call me that.
Just fucking cut it out with this shit.
Don't touch me! I told you!
Fuck!
See. you bring this out in me.
Yeah. I was never this way before. Alice.
None of my exes
ever. ever made me blow up like this.
Why do you think that is?
If we can't talk.
then how do you expect
to move forward. huh?
Huh?
Yeah. sure. run back to Mike.
Why don't you give him another cigarette?
How about a hand job too?
Go to hell!
Joe...
- Hey. no. Will.
- Will. please. you're drunk.
Give me the keys. I'll drive you home.
Will!
Fucking bitch.
Hey. hey. hey. Don't move. Don't...
move.
I'll call 911.
I'll call...
Fuck.
- Fuck!
- Will?
Will?
We found you.
Now lead us to your family.
What the fuck?
Kunda.
Astratta.
Fuck.
Montosse.
Help! Help me! Help!
Help!
Help! Help!
Canda.
Help!
Are you taking anything for sleep?
Hmm?
None of it really works.
When did you guys get in?
Couple of days ago.
Joseph sort of lives here now.
His parents basically gave him
the vacation home.
Look up.
Since when do you have a gun?
That is not mine.
It's Joseph's.
I think he wants to feel badass.
Joseph? Badass?
It's cute.
Hi. Polly. How are you?
She won't remember you.
But it's only been a year. though.
We must be the same size.
Do you think that
with the construction. that we can...
No. no. don't worry.
They promised me they would stop at noon.
and they should be wrapping up
any minute now.
We're gathered here...
We're gathered here today
to celebrate the life of William Price.
To pay tribute.
and to share memories of him.
because for as long as
those memories live on...
William will always be with us.
I would now like to ask Mrs. Susan Price.
William's mother.
to please share a few words.
Bonnie. what are you doing?
No. that's Susan. Grandma.
- Aunt Bonnie isn't with us...
- Don't waste your breath on her.
William.
My sweet boy.
I could go on for hours
about what an amazing child he was.
A model teenager.
And a man who made us so. so proud.
He was so enamored with French cuisine
that when he studied in Paris.
he surprised us
by bringing home a French wife. Alice.
Will dreamed of starting a family.
You two would have made
such outstanding parents.
And we could have been
Grandpa Edgar and Grandma Susan.
I would give anything
for us to be together again.
Thank you. Susan.
And. um. I'm very sorry
about the... the noise.
Alice.
Would you like to share something with us?
A special memory of your husband?
I... I didn't prepare a speech.
Oh...
Okay. um... Wow. Uh...
So...
I would like to play a song that held
a... a special place in William's heart.
Your wedding song.
♪ I want the money. I want the car ♪
♪ I want your woman
be telling me I'm a star ♪
♪ And for the rest of it.
homie. I pray to God ♪
♪ I'm yelling hovah ♪
♪ Halle. halle. hallehovah ♪
♪ Hovah ♪
♪ Halle. halle. halle ♪
♪ What ♪
♪ What these bitches want when they spend ♪
♪ About a dozen summers gettin' real dope ♪
♪ Where they're lookin' at my Twitter
When I have these lil' hoes ♪
♪ Livin'. spittin' like
They think they real pros ♪
♪ With the quote fingers
Hear me. though ♪
♪ I can smell a fraud like a dog do ♪
♪ Talkin' whether it be summer. autumn.
But they fall through ♪
♪ Sue me if you think you
got it better with the boss. fool ♪
♪ This is real rap. motherfucker.
This ain't law school ♪
♪ I just lost a friend
on some pill shit... ♪
I'd like to say goodbye to my son
one last time.
Um. well...
You... You'll be able to collect the ashes
in a couple of days.
- but you're not actually allowed back here.
- Sir.
My son just died.
Five minutes.
And don't tell anyone
or I'll get yelled at.
Thank you.
My condolences.
Fuck!
Will! Will!
Hang on! Hang... Hang on!
Uh... Will! I'm coming!
Will! Hold on. son!
I'm coming! Fuck.
What the fuck?
Help! Help!
- Come with us.
- Okay.
- Okay. We'll see you there.
How far is it?
Damn.
Less than five minutes away.
Fucking...
You okay?
Yeah. no. it's just...
You know they don't want me there.
That's not true.
Kit. in here.
Yeah.
Jesus.
All right. look. The only thing
they care about is that we're all together.
You're part of the family.
Even my mom.
I mean. she said that she was really
touched you agreed to the cremation
instead of the burial.
and we could do it where she wanted.
She appreciates you. Honestly.
Yeah. maybe. I don't know.
Well. I mean. my dad. on the other hand.
I mean. he can't fucking stand you.
Oh. God.
Looks so run-down now.
Wait. you've been here before?
We got married here.
Mom? Dad?
Be right back.
Grandma. You know where Mom is?
Oh.
She's still at school. It lets out at four.
Yeah. Thank you.
Mom?
- What are you doing?
- What do you think?
You invited Alice.
She was Will's wife.
Here. Mom. let me do this.
When we gave you this place.
I asked you to throw everything away.
Why are his things still here?
I just wanted to keep
something from Grandpa.
It felt like I was throwing him away.
He threw us away.
No. I know. It's just...
I mean. some of this stuff.
it's fascinating. you know?
Unleashing flesh-possessing demons
so malevolent as though
the devil himself were here.
Does that sound fascinating to you?
It's just inspiration for my book.
Your book is about Grandpa?
No. not him.
His research. I mean...
Come on. Curses. and demons...
I found all kinds of crazy artifacts
he brought back from around the world.
and apparently he was
part of some secret society.
It was a cult.
They were historians. you know.
And he recorded everything in his notebook.
Look. I was gonna tell you.
No. let me tell you.
- My father was not a good man. Joseph.
- Mom...
When my mom's mind
started to go. he retreated.
Spent more time with
the Circle of the Wise Men than us.
Always off on some expedition.
buried in some stupid old book.
When Aunt Bonnie got sick.
that's when he left us for good.
Hunting for rusty weapons.
Crumbling scrolls.
He said he had to find a way
to protect us from evil.
All he ever did was talk like that
because he didn't have the courage
to face real hardship.
I had to take care of this family.
I'm sorry. Mom.
- You should get some rest.
- It's fine.
I'm fine. It's the pills.
Tell everyone lunch in an hour.
Throw this out.
- Let go of me!
- What's going on?
- She insists on going outside by herself.
- No!
No!
- What are you doing. Polly?
- Grandma!
I was just trying to help!
Bonnie! Bonnie!
I've got her. She's
trying to steal my money.
- Polly!
- Call the police!
- Susan. we were just trying...
- Let go of me.
Bonnie!
- Grandma. are you okay?
- Calm down.
- It's broken.
- Just a sec. Mom.
You thief.
Oh. my God.
Dad?
Dad.
It's out of gas.
You don't need to worry about the yard.
Someone's gotta do it.
- I will. I just haven't had...
- We leave you this house...
and you let it rot.
You like living in shit!
Dad.
Dad. Help me.
We're inside.
Let us in. Dad.
It's okay.
Don't fight.
Come on. you can do it.
Do it.
Do it. Do it.
Edgar?
Edgar. are you okay?
No. no!
Don't tell my wife.
Please.
I'll hold onto this. okay?
Mmm.
- What happened?
- Uh...
I missed a step in the cellar.
I dropped the plates. I'm sorry.
Yes. I heard that.
Would you put this on the dining
room table? Please be careful with it.
Made it myself.
You did?
It's Niobe.
A Greek queen.
- She's Edgar's favorite.
- It's pretty.
Yeah.
Why did you stop?
First. the kids.
Then my sister Bonnie got sick.
And my mother couldn't live on her own.
Well...
You had a gift. It's a shame.
Why is it a shame?
I was with the people I love.
Building a life.
You know. without my family. I'm nothing.
Testing.
Thank you. Joseph.
That was beautiful.
You okay?
Mmm.
I'm good.
No.
That's Will's seat.
Oh. My big boy. Will.
When does he get here?
Edgar. Would you do the wine. please?
Mmm.
Oh. don't worry. I got it.
Mmm. so good.
They're premade. I just heated them.
Joseph is right.
they're... they're delicious.
I would never guess it was frozen.
That's concerning.
Hmm?
It's clearly frozen food on paper plates.
If you manage the restaurant alone.
you'll need to know frozen from fresh.
Mmm.
About the restaurant...
I'm... I'm not sure I plan to...
Let's just talk about it another time.
Let's talk about it now.
We're all here.
Well. I haven't decided anything.
but. I mean. it was Will's restaurant...
You ran the place together.
I only did the accounting.
But you're... his wife.
You sure?
To be honest. I... I was thinking.
I might go back to Paris for a while.
Maybe stay with my... with my dad.
Then things seem
a little more decided than you let on.
No. no. no.
These things should be dealt with
as a family.
Yeah.
We should deal with it as a family.
You know the staff adores you.
Alice. they need you.
Think about Will. Do it for him.
Wait. I recognize you.
You're married to my grandson. aren't you?
Don't turn a deaf ear.
I asked you a question.
It's all right.
- I...
- It's okay. It's okay.
All I'm saying is
you have the chance
to take over a successful business
while honoring Will at the same time.
It was his life's work.
It was his passion.
And you should carry it on.
Susan. I really think
we should do this another time.
No. now's the best time
to lay everything on the table.
He's right.
- We need to make decisions together.
- You are driving me fucking crazy!
Without me you are nothing. Alice.
- It's what Will would have wanted.
- That's Will's seat.
- That's your fucking problem!
- Do it for him.
Will. When does he get here?
We're trying to have a fucking kid!
You do not know what you fucking want!
Say it.
Don't you fucking bait me. Alice.
Alice!
Please. calm down.
I am calm.
But you shouldn't speak on Will's behalf.
I'm his mother.
No one knows him better than I do.
Grandma. no.
Sorry. Okay. look.
We're all here for him.
but I... I think Alice is right.
- This isn't the right time to...
- It's never the right time for you. is it?
That's why you've done nothing
with your life.
Edgar. Please.
- Don't you fucking touch me.
- Edgar.
we're all grieving here.
but that's no reason to be cruel.
- Thya. it's fine.
- It's not.
- Joe...
- Where is it?
Where's the wedding ring?
Why aren't you wearing it?
Did you sell it?
- You get a good price?
- No! No. no. of course not.
- I...
- Edgar. can I have the corkscrew. please?
And a hoodie and sneakers
at her husband's funeral.
I'm right here. Edgar.
You can speak to me directly.
You didn't even cry.
Don't you think that's weird?
People grieve in different...
Get away from me!
Will's dead.
And now you inflict this on us?
That's enough.
Dad. You don't look good...
It's your fault he's dead.
You didn't stop him getting to the car!
Stop it. Dad. I had nothing to do with it.
Will got into a fight with Alice. and he...
What? Are you implying it was my fault?
- No. no. of course not.
- You were there.
You couldn't stop him
from getting in the car either.
I know. Alice. I know. I tried.
We tried. Okay. I didn't.
- That doesn't mean it's my fault.
- That's not what I'm saying...
- This is exactly what you said.
- Alice. no.
- Alice. I think...
- No. I think
you should all mind your own business.
You don't know anything.
You're glad he's dead.
Please. please. please.
Will's looking down on us from above.
From above?
He's down below.
Stop!
The dog!
Help me.
Help me!
- Get your keys.
- Okay.
Let's take him to the hospital!
Thya! I need help! Grab his arm!
I got him! I got him!
What did we do to deserve this?
They left without saying goodbye.
Jesus fucking Christ. is he fucking crazy?
Thya. please. Give me a second.
- He killed your fucking dog!
- I know!
Shit. shit.
He's fucking bleeding everywhere. Shit.
Shit. shit. Come on!
Joe?
- What?
- Your dad.
No! No!
No!
What the fuck?
Oh. my fucking God.
Oh. my God!
Stop!
Let her go!
- Shoot him!
- I said let her go!
Fucking shoot him!
Shoot me. Joe.
Shoot me.
Shoot me. Joe!
Shoot me!
Joseph!
"October. 1983.
That cursed Book of the Dead.
I warned them against reading from it.
The forbidden incantation.
Four words that can unleash evil.
But they didn't listen.
December. 1983.
At last. I have found it.
A weapon that can stop them all.
A dagger created by
the Circle of the Wise Men.
The tiniest cut from this ancient blade
rips their demonic souls from their bodies.
I've hidden it. but now must leave again.
These creatures are hunting me
and I must protect my wife and daughters."
"Kunda."
"Astratta."
"Montosse."
Fuck this.
Get away!
Alice?
What's wrong?
I don't understand you.
What happened?
Where's your father?
I think Dad just killed Thya.
Open up. It's me.
She came back for my money.
To your perfect family.
Cheers.
Joe. it hurts.
- Please. Joe.
- Joe!
- Where is your father?
- We gotta go.
We gotta go. Alice! Alice. come on!
Come on. we gotta go!
Edgar.
- Sweetheart.
- Susan. don't.
- Get off me!
- Mom!
You should be dead.
Not Will.
- No!
He's just standing there.
Staring.
We're fucking trapped!
I'll be right back. Mom.
Ch...
Ch... Children?
Please.
Open the door.
Did you come back
to return what you stole?
Uh...
Oh.
Exactly.
Oh. my God. Mom! Mom.
Are you okay?
Mom? Are you okay?
It's okay. I got you.
You're okay. It's okay.
We will destroy it.
No more wise men.
Should... Should I go.
or do... do you wanna?
You go.
Get Grandma upstairs.
You thought
I'd let you have all the men
in this family to yourself?
Joseph. come!
Help.
Don't bother. babe.
That's not his style.
I said come!
Susan.
Stop coddling the boy.
He has something that we need.
No! No!
Give us what we came for!
I told you she was a thief!
Oh. so you're brave now?
Boo.
I was your first.
And I'll make sure I'm your last.
So you wouldn't shoot your father.
But killing me...
is easy?
Come here. young lady!
I have what you want!
Be right back. baby.
The money's under my mattress.
Take it. and leave us alone.
Aw.
It's all broked in here.
But there is something that we want
in that little head of yours.
Your husband must have told you
where it is.
Huh?
Mmm.
Boop.
This will fix you.
Polly.
Where's your leg?
That little...
The Circle of the Wise Men failed.
Your grandpa failed.
You'll all die tonight.
Alice. Alice. Alice.
I'm coming. Alice.
I'm coming for you.
Fucking say it!
Joe.
What's the Circle of the Wise Men?
I didn't think that it was real.
Please stop hiding stuff.
and just tell me.
I saw those fucked up drawings
you threw out.
Did Will ever tell you
about our grandfather?
Growing up. we were always told
he was unstable.
In his journals. he described it as
this group convinced
the devil had been here.
And would return if anyone
read from what he called...
The Book of the Dead.
My grandfather left his family
to travel the world.
researching and collecting artifacts
as protection from all this.
You still have them?
My mom asked me to throw everything
away after he died. but...
- Fucking...
- No. no no.
She asked. but I didn't.
There's still some stuff
hidden up in the attic.
And Thya.
that thing inside her.
said they were looking for something.
Maybe whatever that is.
it can stop them.
Mom? I need you to drink this. please.
Can you look under the bed?
Daddy always checks
to make sure there aren't any monsters.
No monsters.
You're lying.
Don't worry.
You're safe here.
Goodnight. Mom.
Goodnight. Susan.
What did you call me?
Come. sweetheart.
Mom.
I missed you.
I missed you so much.
We share the same dream.
It can still come true.
The whole family can be reunited.
Will's already on his way.
He'll be here soon.
Don't be scared. Susan.
Remember what you said at the funeral.
That you would give everything you have
for us all to be together again.
Without your family. you're nothing.
I miss you.
I miss us.
You haven't kissed me
like that in years.
Your father's not there anymore.
Maybe we can...
Joseph?
Hey. is... is Grandma
okay? Everything good?
Yes. everything's better now.
I need you to trust me.
Trust you?
They're not our enemies.
I realize that now.
They just want something back
that my father stole.
I told you. he was a bad man.
It's simple.
Tell them where it is.
Give them what they want. and this ends.
We can be happy again.
Where what is?
A weapon.
But we threw everything away.
You're lying to me.
Tell us where it is.
Us?
Where is the Kandarian dagger?
No! No!
Alice! Alice. run!
Leave us alone!
You need to stop meddling
in our family affairs.
You promised!
You promised not to hurt him!
Finally some use
for this revolting piece of shit.
Come.
See what you did.
Finally. something you can be proud of.
Did you say something?
I know where the dagger is!
Nothing will stand in our way now.
Once we have the dagger...
No!
Get off him!
- Edgar! Get off!
- Fuck.
Get off me!
Help me! Help me!
No! No!
Where's the dagger?
Where is it?
Answer me!
Find it.
Before them.
No!
Oh. stop.
I'm just giving you what you want.
I know you liked it when Will hurt you.
Isn't that why you stayed?
Don't turn a deaf ear.
I asked you a question.
Susan.
Help.
Susan. dear.
Would you mind pushing the throttle
to tear this bitch's face off. please?
She brought chaos into this family.
Your son died because of her.
Do it.
For Will.
Do it!
Oh. Susan.
Do it.
I'm sorry. Alice.
Is it Joseph?
Is it my son?
What are you doing?
You should be grateful
I didn't leave you back there.
Don't you dare move.
Grateful?
My family is gone.
Everyone I love is gone.
Because of you.
All you've ever done is bring us pain.
I hate you.
Oh. shut up. Susan!
Shut the fuck up!
I didn't bring anything to your family.
It was already there.
You see this?
You see. Susan? This is your son.
This is what he was capable of.
- Was an accident!
- No! It wasn't!
It was not. And you knew.
You knew. Susan.
You deserve everything
that's happened to you.
Every fucking thing.
But you know what?
It's behind me now.
I don't give a shit anymore.
You're right.
Your past is behind you.
Right... Right behind you.
Like a shadow.
Can't escape it.
Just when you think you're safe.
Healed.
When you breathe a quivering sigh.
my son will be there.
As a husband should.
And he will burn you down
like the whore you are.
You will be dead by dawn!
Alice.
Help me up.
I know where the dagger is.
I'll help you find it.
And then I'll cut you open with it
like my brother should have.
You're worthless.
Just like my grandfather.
Shut up!
He never found it. and you never will.
Let me end your miserable life.
You like pain anyway.
That's why you let Will hurt you.
Isn't it?
Poor little Alice.
You'll be found in an attic alone.
Gutted from tit to tail.
You never wanted kids anyway.
Your body is useless.
Wrong one.
The Circle of the Wise Men is dead.
Come here. you little bitch.
I told you it's not here.
My family will...
Fuck your family!
Did you stay because you liked it?
Or you were
too much of a coward to leave me?
Look at you now.
You still can't leave.
Remember the last thing you said to me?
"Go to hell."
You got your wish.
I shouldn't have hurt you. Alice.
I should have killed you.
This is where I promised
I'd always be with you.
Where I promised that
not even death would do us part.
I will keep my promise. Alice.
'Cause without me.
you are nothing.
Hello?
Hello? Hello...
I could never have lived
without you. Alice.
I won't let you live without me.
Shit.
Where is the dagger?
Where is it?
Where is it. Alice?
Go get it.
Where is the dagger?
Speak or burn. bitch!
Here's your fucking dagger!
I love you.
That's not enough.
Got a cigarette?
- I'm not really allowed to...
- Just give it to me.
Who did this to you?
My ex-husband.
Wicked little French bitch.
Ma'am! What happened? Are you okay?
Oh. thank heaven! Please help me!
She stole my legs!
But yours will do just fine.
Yes. sweetie. I know.
It's no fun coming into work
with me on a Saturday.
But I've had to do everything
by myself since...
Well. you know.
I'll make it up to you tonight.
How come you're keeping
all these urns full of dead people?
Uh...
Well...
it's sad. actually.
These are the people
whose families never came for them.
So. we keep them here for a few months
in case a family member
remembers to pick them up one day.
Okay. Don't touch anything. okay?
That might be about the cremator job.
I'll be right back.
"Christopher Leroy."
"Ellie Bixler."
Hey.
Mom?
Don't be scared. baby.
Mommy's back.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today